We're going to talk about the next twist, the full twist.
This twist is a little bit more common than most of the balloon animals you'll see, in fact most of them use them for legs and that sort of thing.
I don't use it quite as often, but any time you need a graceful leaf or petal on a flower, what you do is you fold it over how big you want it, and once you make a twist you go ahead and make another twist and twist it inside of it.
Once again, big as you need it to be and fold it over and I turn it as I twist it into itself.
It just seems to help it get in there a little bit easier.
Now this would be the stem for a flower.
What you do for a flower itself is actually use a different color.
You make about four to six full twists.
In this case I'm just going to tie the knot around itself.
The next one goes around, twist it in, again twist it in, twist it in, twist it in.
The final petal, use the uninflated end of the balloon and sort of tie it around.
This bubble you've created end, twist it in there for a fairly quick and easy flower that's likely to please anyone's girlfriend.